tagstyle.com 2015-11-21

# Tagstyle | Privacy Policy

Tagstyle (Tagstyle Pte Ltd) respects the privacy rights of our customers and we will only track statistics for business purposes. No private information will be disclosed to unrelated entities or any third party merchants unless required by law. All email addresses in our mailing list are strictly kept confidential. 

This Privacy Policy applies to personal data collected, stored, disclosed and/or processed by Tagstyle. 

This Policy is based on the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012 ("PDPA") and all of the associated regulations and guidelines may vary from time to time as per issue by the Personal Data Protection Commission ("PDPC") of Singapore. Tagstyle’s practices may be subjected to different or more restrictive local laws in jurisdictions outside of Singapore. 

By visiting or using the Tagstyle website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully before visiting, using our website, or providing us with any of your personal data. 

Information is collected from you when you subscribe to our newsletter; fill out any forms and via cookies. Data that Tagstyle collects or stores may, subject to applicable law and the PDPA, be transferred to and used by us outside of Singapore. It will be treated according to the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**Personal Data**

Data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics may be used to: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To send periodic emails (the email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.) 

When ordering or registering on our site, personal data includes, among other things, your: name; street or mailing address; telephone number(s); email addresses; date of birth; gender; nationality; purchases of products; payment information; credit card numbers; marketing preferences; answers you provide to security questions (such as your mother's maiden name, the name of your pet, etc.); information used to provide products or services; information needed to administer rewards or loyalty programs, including transaction and correspondence details; and any other types of information that you choose to provide to us or that we may collect about you through your transactions with Tagstyle.

Information collected under Tagstyle will be retained under the authority of Tagstyle Pte Ltd. In the event of a sale of any Tagstyle Pte Ltd’s asset including customer information, buyers will be required to honor our Privacy Policy or provide you a notice and option to limit the sharing of your information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future email notifications, we have included detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**Protection of Information**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Usage of Cookies**

When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more "cookies." By accessing our website, you agree that we can place cookies on your device. 

A cookie is a small text file that contains information that can later be read by us to facilitate your access to our website, gather statistical data, and personalize your online experience. We currently use cookies on our website for purposes including, but not limited to, detecting your web browser's multimedia capabilities, tracking promotional advertisements that we have displayed to you, maintaining current login and providing a unique identifier to your computer so that we can generate statistics regarding website usage. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies. Generally, you can remove these cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. If you choose not to allow us to place a cookie on your computer, you may be restricted from some services and some of the interactive features offered on our websites may be similarly restricted or rendered inoperable. 

In addition to cookies, we may also use other Internet technologies, such as web beacons or pixel tags, and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of our website. The information we obtain in this manner enables us measure the overall effectiveness of our online content, advertising campaigns, and the products we offer through our website. By accessing our website and agreeing to receive our email messages or newsletters, you agree to that we can use other Internet technologies such as those mentioned above on your device(s). 

Our website may allow third parties to download cookies to your device(s). Third parties, such as Google Analytics, may use cookies and other technologies to collect non-personal data about your online activities while you are on our website. This information may be used to measure usage of our website and personalize advertising content on our website. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features these third parties may use, and this Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of these third parties. Please refer to the privacy policies of those third parties to better understand their activities and practices. 

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Non-disclosure Agreement**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as these parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect others and our rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Opt-Out**

If you do not want your personal data to be shared among affiliates, you may opt-out of such information sharing by sending us an email at customerservice@tagstyle.com. Please note that if you withdraw your consent for a limited purpose, such as for marketing, we may still contact you or use your information for other purposes for which you have not withdrawn your consent and such personal data may still be shared, as permitted under the PDPA and other applicable law. If you do not wish to receive any further information from Tagstyle regarding launches, offers, promotions or special events via email, you may unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link in our mailers. 

**Usage of Site**

Tagstyle may feature pictures, articles, information, digital images, text, data, games, surveys, contests, promotions, advertising, logos, trademarks and other forms of content*** we deem will be of interest to our customers or visitors. This Content can be viewed, transferred, shared and stored by our customers and guest. However, the ownership of this Content belongs to tagstyle.com and by downloading or storing of this Content does not render the customer or visitor the rights or ownership to it. 

***Collectively, content composite one or more of the following - text, data, music, sound, graphics, images, pictures, photographs, videos, software or other forms later created or not known at this time. 

Content extracted from tagstyle.com and published or shared on any platforms must be credited. Tagstyle Pte. Ltd. reserves the rights to pursue legal actions against unauthorized usage of this Content. 

**Security**

Tagstyle practices reasonable precautions to protect your personal data and store it securely. However, you should be aware that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage has 100% security. While security cannot be guaranteed, we strive to protect the security of your information and are constantly reviewing and enhancing our information security measures. Tagstyle’s website has security measures in place that strive to protect against the accidental loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information while under our control. Such security measures include, but are not limited to, password controls, firewalls, and other industry standard security measures.

**Privacy Policy Amendments**

Tagstyle (Tagstyle Pte. Ltd.) reserves the rights to amend any of the policies above at any time. The Effective Date, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was materially revised. We encourage you to review this page periodically as changes may be made to our policy from time to time regarding the collection and use of your personal data. 

Your continued use of our website and acceptance of our services after any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to any such changes; to the extent such consent is not otherwise provided. 

**For more information on our Privacy Policy, please contact us at[customerservice@tagstyle.com](mailto:customerservice@tagstyle.com). **

(Last updated on 1 March 2015)
